[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "64",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "69",
        "66",
        "64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "-1",
        "1",
        "3",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "options": [
        "38",
        "36",
        "41",
        "34"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "25",
        "30",
        "23",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "81",
      "options": [
        "79",
        "83",
        "86",
        "81"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "25",
        "30",
        "23",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "81",
      "options": [
        "86",
        "83",
        "81",
        "79"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "-1",
        "1",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "30",
        "23",
        "25",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "9",
        "2",
        "6"
      ]
    }
]